CURRICULUM VITAE



Rufaida Jumaa

Address: Frødalen 24 1sal tv, 3400 Hillerød

Born 01/01/1993



+45 20710141



E-mail



GitHub



LinkedIn

SKILLS

HTML/CSS JavaScript(ES6) NodeJS MySQL React Git Sitecore

LANGUAGES

Umbraco

Arabic
Danish Dansk3-Module 4
English
French (A2 Spoken, A2 written)

PROFILE

I am an ambitious and curious person with a great passion for Web Development. Since I moved to Denmark, back in 2017, I have learned 2 languages, English and Danish, studied Web Development intensively and joined Kruso as a web developer but I had to interrupt my career because I became a mother for the second time. I am now ready to embrace a career as a Web Developer where I can use my WebDevelopment skills from the HackYourFuture Full Stack course and *work experience* together with my Information Technology Engineering background.

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2018 – 11/2018 KRUSO A/S - Copenhagen/ Denmark
Frontend Developer Working mainly with Umbraco, Sitecore, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

02/2018 – 08/2018 KRUSO A/S - Copenhagen/ Denmark

Developer internship Working with various small backend & frontend development tasks and working within different departments of the company.

EDUCATION

05/2017 – 14/1/2018 - HackYourFuture - Copenhagen/ Denmark
Full Stack Web Development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL with Express,
React, GIT

09/2011 – 11/2016 - DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY - Damascus/ Syria

Bachelor of Information Technology Engineering - Computer Systems and Networks
5 year education, Received Bachelor of Science, GPA (73.64)
(equivalent to the Danish "professions-bachelor som diplomingeniør - IT")

2010 – 08/2011 - SYRIAN MINISTRY OF EDUCATION - Damascus/ Syria General Certificate Of Secondary Education (Scientific Section) Focus on Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry and Natural Sciences, Arabic, English and French, GPA (95.83)